Fight the system. Change the world.
Altered is a science fiction, action film directed by Timo Vuorensola.
In an alternate present, genetically enhanced humans dominate society.
Outcasts Leon and Chloe fight for justice against corrupt politicians exploiting
genetic disparity, risking everything to challenge the oppressive system.
Leon, played by Tom Felton.
Mira, played by Aggy K. Adams.
Chloe, played by Elizaveta Bugulova.
Frank Kessler, played by Richard Brake.
Cook, played by Aleksey Filimonov.
Altered is a 2024 American science fiction action film
written and directed by Timo Vuorensola.
It stars Tom Felton, Liza Bugulova, Richard Brake, Igor Jijikine and Aggy K.
The tone is thought_provoking.